<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title></title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-09-11T21:34:22.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Trinity | Shalay | Tanner</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why we need more women in tech</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2017-08-31T01:37:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-09-11T21:34:22.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<html><br>    <head><br>        <title>Why we need more women in tech</title><br>        <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="styles.css"><br>    </head><br>    <body><br>        <img src="/../women-in-tech-pinup.jpg"><br>        <h3>Hedy Lamarr</h3><br>        <p>Lamarr was a pin-up girl in the 1930’s but in the 1940s she started helping George Anthiel with tech, She became a pioneer in wireless technologies, while working with george she developed a radio guidance system for torpedoes. This technology is now being used for Bluetooth, GPS, and Wi-Fi. She was given a special award in 1997 for “trail-blazing development of a technology that has become a key component of wireless data systems.”</p><br>    </body><br></html>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;html&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;head&gt;&lt;br&gt;        &lt;title&gt;Why we need more women in tech&lt;/title&gt;&lt;br&gt;        &lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; href=&quot;styles
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="1" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/1/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Grace Hopper</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/Another-Blog-Post/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/Another-Blog-Post/</id>
    <published>2017-08-30T23:10:54.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-09-11T21:34:28.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<html><br><head><br>    <title></title><br></head><br><body><br>    <img src="/../First-Women-in-Tech-2.jpg"><br>    <h3>Grace Hopper</h3><br>    <p>An early woman in tech, Dr. Hopper was one of the first programmers of the Harvard Mark I computer. She was the first female to graduate the Ph.D. program at Yale with a focus in mathematics. She was also the first woman to reach the rank of Admiral in the United States Navy. Her list of accomplishments goes on, including developing the Common Business-Oriented Language (COBOL) and popularizing the term “bug” for a glitch.<br><br>The U.S. Navy destroyer USS Hopper is named for her. At the age of 79, Hopper retired as the oldest active-duty commissioned officer in the U.S. Navy. She continued with public speaking after her military retirement and was quoted as saying that training young people and inspiring them to take chances was one of the most important things she accomplished. The U.S. Naval Academy plans to name its future cyber building after her.<br><br>These are just a few of the current and past women in tech who have made immeasurable contributions to global technology, often against the odds. Their contributions to technology are huge, as are their contributions in laying a foundation for the proliferation of women in technology that is only starting to come to pass.</p><br></body><br></html>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;html&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;title&gt;&lt;/title&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;img src=&quot;/../First-Women-in-Tech-2.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;h3&gt;Grace Hopper&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;b
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="2" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/2/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Ada Lovelace</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/First-Blog-Post/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/First-Blog-Post/</id>
    <published>2017-08-30T23:10:54.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-09-11T21:39:13.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<html><br><head><br>    <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="styles.css"><br></head><br><body><br>    <div class="image"><br>        <img src="/../women-in-tech-ada.jpg"><br>        <h3>Ada Lovelace aka (Algorithm Enchantress)</h3><br>        <p>Her impact on technology:<br>Ada Lovelace was unique in that she developed an algorithm for a computer that didn’t yet exist — an accomplishment that some say qualifies her as the world’s first computer programmer.<br><br>Born to English nobility in 1815, Lovelace was put to work by Charles Babbage in 1843, documenting his never-to-be-realized “computer,” the Analytical Engine. Starting with a document written in French by Luigi Menabrea, an Italian mathematician, Lovelace added extensive notes to the English translation, including the world’s first computer algorithm.<br><br>The Analytical Engine was intended to count Bernoulli numbers, but Babbage was unsuccessful in getting the funding to build his machine. Notably, Lovelace was able to see the potential for the computer beyond simple math.<br><br>“Many persons who are not conversant with mathematical studies imagine that because the business of [Babbage’s Analytical Engine] is to give its results in numerical notation, the nature of its processes must consequently be arithmetical and numerical, rather than algebraical and analytical. This is an error. The engine can arrange and combine its numerical quantities exactly as if they were letters or any other general symbols; and in fact it might bring out its results in algebraical notation, were provisions made accordingly,” Lovelace wrote in the Sketch of the Analytical Engine Invented by Charles Babbage, Esq.<br><br></p><br>    </div><br>    <p></p><br></body><br></html>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;html&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; href=&quot;styles.css&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;div class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;       
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="3" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/3/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sample Blog Post</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/Sample-Blog-Post/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/Sample-Blog-Post/</id>
    <published>2017-08-30T23:10:46.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-09-11T21:34:19.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<html><br><head><br>    <title>Sample Blog Post</title><br>    <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="styles.css"><br></head><br><body><br>    <div class="image"><br>        <img src="first-women-in-tech.jpg"><br>    </div><br>    <p></p><br></body><br></html>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;html&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;title&gt;Sample Blog Post&lt;/title&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; href=&quot;styles.css&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;body
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="4" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Shalays Blog post</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/ShalaysBlog/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/08/30/ShalaysBlog/</id>
    <published>2017-08-30T23:10:46.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-09-11T21:34:17.000Z</updated>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="5" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/5/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
